<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeSustainable</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Firebase String -->
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">alerts</string>


    <!-- Sustainable Titles -->
    <string name="principe1">Principle 1 – Reliability</string>
    <string name="principe2">Principle 2 – Relevance</string>
    <string name="principe3">Principle 3 - Clarity</string>
    <string name="principe4">Principle 4 - Transparency</string>
    <string name="principe5">Principle 5 - Accessibility</string>
    <string name="principe6">Principle 6 – Three Dimensions of Sustainability</string>
    <string name="principe7">Principle 7 – Behavior Change &amp; Longer Term Impact</string>
    <string name="principe8">Principle 8 – Multi-channel &amp; Innovative Approach</string>
    <string name="principe9">Principle 9 - Collaboration</string>
    <string name="principe10">Principle 10 - Comparability</string>

    <!-- Sustainable - Questions -->
    <string name="principe1_Reliability">Do you see any information related to sustainability? \n If so, is it certified or supported by standardized methods, governments, NGOs or a scientific organization?</string>
    <string name="principe2_Relevance">Is this sustainability information focused on the topics that you consider more important about sustainability taking into account the geography where it has been produced and where it will be used or consumed?</string>
    <string name="principe3_Clarity">Is the sustainability information clear, concise and intuitive enough to understand the environmental performance of this product? Does it allow you to understand the environmental impact of the product?</string>
    <string name="principe4_Transparency">Do you have enough information to evaluate the sustainability of the product?</string>
    <string name="principe5_Accesibility">Is the information clearly visible? Does it offer complementary information?</string>
    <string name="principe6_Three_Dimensions_of_Sustainability">Does the sustainability information cover environmental, social and economic aspects? Does it allow you to understand why the product is sustainable within these 3 components? </string>
    <string name="principe7_Behavior_Change_Longer_Term_Impact">Does it advice you about how to reduce the impact on sustainability during the use and disposal of it? Does it encourage you to have a more sustainable behavior?</string>
    <string name="principe8_Multi_Chanel_Innovate_Approach">Is the way of transmitting information about sustainability innovative? Does it offer you different channels to access it?</string>
    <string name="principe9_Collaboration">Has the provided information taken into account the opinion and collaboration of the different groups of interest? Does this information make you feel part of a larger movement within sustainability?</string>
    <string name="principe10_Comparability">Does it allow you to compare the product in terms of sustainability with other products in the same category or sector?</string>
    
    <!--IP address Server -->
    <!-- Change the ip if you work by way of Local -->
    <string name="ip">http://192.168.1.10</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
